<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Victor Le</title>
    <link>https://victorchanle.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Victor Le</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://victorchanle.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Current Role</title>
      <link>https://victorchanle.com/projects/frontier-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victorchanle.com/projects/frontier-communications/</guid>
      <description>TLDR
At Frontier Communications, I enabled powerful analyses of disparate datasets by developing and maintaining complex cloud-based ETL pipelines. Subsequently, I built robust, predictive models and dashboards to empower network operations teams&amp;rsquo; responses to customer service issues.
Description Though exact details are proprietary, I will highlight the breadth of the work that I&amp;rsquo;ve performed at Frontier Communcations. For context, Frontier Communications is a large-sized telecommunications company, aiming to provide fiber and copper service across the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academia</title>
      <link>https://victorchanle.com/projects/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victorchanle.com/projects/research/</guid>
      <description>Academic Research At the University of Michigan in Ann Arbor, I researched specific applications of wearable technology for health monitoring. In particular, I researched the intersection of data science, signal processing, and biomechanics to enhance secondary prevention of motion sickness and dehydration. In these excerpts, I&amp;rsquo;ll quickly summarize the tangible, experimental work I completed.
For context, an abstract is copied below. For an in-depth look at the whole body of work, please refer to my dissertation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://victorchanle.com/projects/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victorchanle.com/projects/music/</guid>
      <description>a personal project between me and my friends. i hit things.
so far, we&amp;rsquo;ve released two singles; expect an EP soon!
Spotify</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>https://victorchanle.com/projects/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victorchanle.com/projects/photography/</guid>
      <description>Yes I know they&amp;rsquo;re mostly my dogs Pictures of my little family unit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
